

# Rifqi Finaldy

Frontend Developer Click here to Visit my Portfolio

### **About Me**

Experienced Frontend Developer in developing and driving projects forward from concept into production ready. Currently addicted to **React** and enthusiasted with **Javascript**. Easily inspired and prefer to keep learning and continue to challenging myself as "Skills can be taught and Personality is inherent".

### Skills

**HTML** 

CSS

Javascript

EJS

React

Next

Redux)

Typescript )

Bootstrap

MaterialUI

Framer Motion

Flask

### Tools

- Figma
- Adobe (PS, Illustrator, XD)
- Balsamiq
- Contentful

### **Education**



2012 - 2015

23 Senior High School

Science Major



2015 - 2020

#### National Institute of Technology

Informatic Engineering (3.28 GPA), Head Director of Art Division of HMIF Itenas

### **Experience**

### Frontend Developer Intern

#### Passion IT



🚞 July 2018 - September 2018

- Design & Build Dynamic Company Profile Website
- Design mockup based on user requirement
- Translate UI/UX into fully functional Code

#### Frontend Developer

PT. Transformasi Data Indonesia (SocketSpace)



April 2021 - April 2022

- Collaborated with designer team in concepting and analyzing projects.
- Assisted in creating reusable code, components, and library for future use.
- Developed and maintained website and landing pages frontend code on 7+ projects.
- Optimize user friendliness and performance on the client side.

## Training & Certificate

#### InformIT



October 2019 - January 2020

Python (Flask) Programming Language Training to integrate with Webapp (HTML, CSS, JS).



October 2019

ipV6 Configuration training using CiscoPacket Tracer.

#### **MyEduSolve**



October 2020

Basic Graphic Design Fundamental Training.